Welcome to Mine project's solo exhibition of highly
talented American emerging artist Austin Lee on easel.
Lee, a sought after New York artist,
showcases his playful, airbrushed acrylic paintings alongside
captivating foam sculptures that mark an exciting
new direction in his artistic journey.
It is within this context that Lee further explores
the impact of image editing software on the visual
languages of painting and sculpture, providing viewers with a
glimpse into his unmistakable psychedelic stylings.
Prepare to be captivated by a diverse collection
of leans, paintings and foam sculptures that seamlessly
blend abstraction and figuration, while skillfully incorporating elements
of both humor and pathos.